Gabriel Allen Paul Lopez

UX/UI Designer | Creative Strategist

gabedesigns.me

Versatile and ambitious creative strategist with 4+ years of experience in professional image curation and digital marketing best practices coupled with an eye for modern design principles and a strong understanding of user connections, shaping me as a valuable addition to any team. Seeking an exceptional full-time role in the field of UX/UI design.



EDUCATION

2022 University of California, Irvine (Jan 2022 - July 2022)

Division of Continuing Education UX/UI Design Bootcamp Certificate

2020 University of California, Irvine (Sept 2016 - June 2020)

Bachelor of Arts in Education Sciences minor in Business Management



WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 O Glidewell Dental Laboratories

Social Media Strategist (Paid Media) (July 2021 - Present)

- · Utilizes collected data from the performance reports to perform A/B testing and seek opportunities to enhance social media efforts.
- · Collaborates with cross-functional teams, including marketing, sales and customer service to ensure brand consistency.
- · Creates robust lead generation funnels for prospecting and increasing followership using paid advertisement.
- · Manages 10+ social media based projects per month in accordance to brand strategy and content frequency.

2022 **♦ GVBE Photography**

Freelance Photographer (Sept 2017 - Present)

gvbephoto.com

- · Executes event planning with clients to coordinate and provide cohesive itineraries to ensure high quality customer service and detail-oriented work.
- · Curates wedding, graduation, and personal photo sessions.
- · Manages online business presence for platforms such as Instagram, Facebook, and LinkedIn.

2021 • Creative Solutions for Hope

Social Media Coordinator (Jan 2021 - July 2021)

- · Implemented a results-driven social media strategy aimed to increase brand awareness and client-intake conversions.
- · Enhanced user experience for the company website by implementing new client intake forms and employee training resources on a bi-monthly basis.
- · Improved search engine optimization (SEO) results utilizing Google Analytics to improve client-intake form conversions frequently.

2020 • Fusion of Ideas

Production Assistant (Sept 2020 - Jan 2021)

- · Analyze warehouse production processes to ensure efficient and cohesive plans to meet 15+ project deadlines per week.
- · Assist the customization of printing and packaging electronics for 10+ project samples per day in order to meet sample of agreements.

Contact

+1 619-841-8513

gabrielallenpaullopez@gmail.com

dribbble.com/gvbedesigns

instagram.com/gvbephoto

Technical

linkedin.com/in/gabrielallenpaullopez



SKILLS

Personal

Creative Thinking Teamwork

Communication Organization

Leadership Critical Thinkin

Public Speaking Empathy

Teamwork User Research Figma
Organization Interviewing Content Planning
Critical Thinking Visual Prototyping Project Management

A/B Testing Social Media
UX Writing Photography

HTML/CSS SEO



Teaching

Solution Oriented

PROJECTS

2022 **2020-2022** Graduation Services

- Strategized marketing for client services within popular colleges located in California. Coordinated itineraries and location-scouting for 50+ clients within a 3-month period.
- Tools used: Sony A7RIII, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Acrobat Pro,
 Calendly, Google Calendar

2022 MDES (Mississippi Department of Employment Services)

- Developed a cohesive redesign for the MDES website aimed to improve and support individuals seeking unemployment aid.
- Tools used: Figma, Miro, A/B Testing. Usability Testing, User Journey, Site Map, Gestalt Laws, and design principles

2022 HaloEd (Mobile Immersive Learning)

- Designed a mobile application created for individuals seeking to adopt new skills or new hobbies on top of their everyday duties.
- Tools used: Figma, Miro, sketching, user interviews, proto-personas, competitive analysis, user journeys, creative matrix



HOBBIES AND INTEREST









ACHIEVEMENTS AND CERTIFICATIONS

UX/UI Design Boot Camp (July 2022)
University of California, Irvine

Google Certifications: Mobile Strategy (Sept 2021)

Google Skillshop

2021 LinkedIn Course Path: Project Management (July 2021)
LinkedIn Learning

2016 State Seal of Biliteracy (June 2016)
California Department of Education